Always bring protection.
Scouts Guide to the Zombie Apocalypse is a comedy,
horror film directed by Christopher Landon.
Three scouts and lifelong friends join forces with one badass cocktail
waitress to become the world’s most unlikely team of heroes.
When their peaceful town is ravaged by a zombie invasion, they’ll fight for the badge of a
lifetime and put their scouting skills to the test to save mankind from the undead.
Ben Goudy, played by Tye Sheridan.
Denise Russo, played by Sarah Dumont.
Carter Grant, played by Logan Miller.
Augie Foster, played by Joey Morgan.
Jeff, played by Patrick Schwarzenegger.
Scout Leader Rogers, played by David Koechner.
Scouts Guide to the Zombie Apocalypse is a 2015 American zombie comedy film directed by
Christopher Landon, and written by Landon, Carrie Evans, Emi Mochizuki and Lona Williams.
The film stars Tye Sheridan, Logan Miller, Joey
Morgan, Sarah Dumont and David Koechner.
The film was released in the United States on
October 30, 2015, by Paramount Pictures.
It received generally negative reviews from critics
but Sheridan's performance was praised.
The film explores themes of shotgun, camping, campsite, gore, strip club.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.